<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Programming on Blog of Dylan Legendre</title>
    <link>https://blog.dylanlegendre.com/tags/programming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Programming on Blog of Dylan Legendre</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 10:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.dylanlegendre.com/tags/programming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2026: New Year New Beginnings</title>
      <link>https://blog.dylanlegendre.com/posts/2026/new-year-new-beginnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 10:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.dylanlegendre.com/posts/2026/new-year-new-beginnings/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;an-introduction&#34;&gt;An Introduction&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As 2025 draws to a close and we greet the new year, I&amp;rsquo;m drawn to think about my New Year&amp;rsquo;s Resolutions. It sounds cliche, but I wanted to try some new things this year. I&amp;rsquo;ll start by introducing myself. My name is Dylan Legendre. While online I go by my gamer tag alias &amp;ldquo;MorpheusZero&amp;rdquo;, and a lot of my friends just call me &amp;ldquo;Morph&amp;rdquo; for short. The name came about when I was a young teenager and I had to create my first PlayStation Profile. At the time, and still today, I was a huge fan of The Matrix movies and the name just came from that. As of this writing, I am currently 35 years old, a dad to a 3 year old (soon-to-be a dad again), a husband, and I work professionally as a Software Engineer. I graduated from Nicholls State University in Thibodaux, Louisiana in 2014 with a degree in Business Administration while studying as part of the Computer Information Systems (CIS) program. So let&amp;rsquo;s get the easy thing out of the way—I don&amp;rsquo;t have a Computer Science Degree. It&amp;rsquo;s because at the time, the University didn&amp;rsquo;t offer a CS Degree program. So I had to work harder to get myself into programming after school.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
